# BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# Nahuel Brandán

EMAIL: contact@nahuelbrandan.com | WEB: www.nahuelbrandan.com/en |







# ABOUT ME 🔿

Backend Software Developer, specialized in the Python ecosystem, with more than 3 years of experience in the industry, ultimately working in the aerospace industry.

Pragmatic. Proactive. Promoter of constant improvement in technical documentation and application of good development practices. Always in constant learning.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Company: <u>Satellogic</u> | 06/2022 - 09/2022

Company specialized in earth observation satellites. Design, manufacture, and operate his own fleet of satellites.

I was part of the backend development team, based on Python, of satellite flight applications, dealing with highly complex problems.

# Company: Ascentio Technologies | Project: Sabia-Mar | 08/2021 - 05/2022

Sabia-Mar is a satellite mission, with advanced technology for the study of the sea and the ocean.

I worked as a software developer in **Python**, making contributions to different communication and flight planning modules of the satellite. Developer of both the software and the validation tests. Working with technologies like: Robot Framework, Docker, FastAPI, Django, APIs.

### **Company:** <u>IncluIT</u> | **Project:** <u>Junar</u> | 03/2019 - 07/2021

- Performing development activities in Python + Django + Django Rest Framework.
- Integration of Autho and Keyclok as a security layer to an API Management.
- Development related to **Elastic Search**, **Redis**, **Celery**.

# EDUCATION (

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER ANALYST - (COMPLETED)**

#### Faculty of Mathematics, Astronomy, Physics and Computing - UNC | 10/2018

Career with strong emphasis on programming, analysis and design of systems, databases and computer networks, without neglecting the theoretical aspects that sustain them.

# SELF-STUDY ONLINE COURSES | Platzi | 01/2021 - Present

More than **100 courses completed** and in constant learning in the Platzi professional online academy, on various topics such as: soft skills, English, software development.

# SKILLS (

- Programming languages: Python, C.
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, Elastic Search.
- Frameworks: Django, FastAPI, Robot FW.
- Others: Linux, API Rest, Django, Git, Bash, Autho, Docker, FastAPI, Robot FW.

# EXTRAS C

English: B1 intermediate.

• Spanish: Native.







